YOJHAN RODRIGUEZ

https://ylrodriguez.github.io/Portfolio/



ylrodriguez024@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ylrodriguez/



https://github.com/ylrodriguez

Education

Telematics Engineering

Universidad Distrital Bogota, Colombia 2019

Systems and Data Technology

Universidad Distrital Bogota, Colombia 2016

English as a Second Language Program

University of North Carolina Wilmington, United States 2015

Skills

HTML

CSS3

JavaScript

Angular 2+

Material

MySQL

Professional Profile

I am a web developer with 3+ years of experience, passionate about technology, programming and languages, willing to face new challenges and learn different things every day.

I consider myself as a highly responsible person with broad knowledge in different front-end tools such as Angular 2+, JavaScript, HTML5, TypeScript, **Bootstrap**, **Foundation** among others. Additionally, I am always committed to keep learning new technologies and improve my skills.

At last, I consider important to mention that I have an interest in other cultures and languages which have allowed me to be fluent in English.

Work Experience

Grupo Cincoveinticinco: Front-end Engineer

April 2020 - May 2022

Develop and maintain in-house and clients' software mainly for cinema and television networks using different languages, platforms, frameworks and tools such as Javascript, Typescript, Angular, Material, Ruby on Rails, etc.

In addition, architect and implement front-end solutions to meet different requirements from clients as Netflix, Sony Pictures, Telemundo and RCN Colombia.

Freelancer: Front-end Developer

February 2019 - March 2020

Develop and maintain user interfaces and web applications using tools as HTML5, CSS3, Angular 2+, SASS, Bootstrap, Foundation, SVG animations and REST services.

Update legacy software and improve user interfaces from different local companies such as Casa Luker, Jgb and Tybasoft.

Universidad Distrital: Jr. Software Developer

January 2018 - July 2018

Manage and maintain internal web applications using Angular, JavaScript, Laravel and MySQL according to all the needs of the internal software and also one main project called "Conocí-Siento".

Develop and adapt existing modules to generate reports and final products.

YOJHAN RODRIGUEZ

https://ylrodriguez.github.io/Portfolio/



ylrodriguez024@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ylrodriguez/



https://github.com/ylrodriguez

Educación

Ingeniero en Telemática

Universidad Distrital Bogotá, Colombia 2019

Tecnólogo en Sistematización de datos

Universidad Distrital Bogotá, Colombia 2016

English as a Second Language Program

Universidad de Carolina del Norte Wilmington, Estados Unidos 2015

Habilidades

HTML

CSS3

JavaScript

Angular 2+

Material

MySQL

Perfil Profesional

Soy desarrollador web con 3+ años de experiencia, apasionado por la tecnología, la programación y los idiomas, dispuesto a asumir nuevos retos y aprender cosas nuevas cada día.

Me considero una persona con alto sentido de responsabilidad y compromiso que posee amplios conocimientos en diferentes herramientas de desarollo front-end como Angular 2+, JavaScript, HTML5. CSS3. TypeScript. Bootstrap entre otros. resaltando mi compromiso en seguir aprendiendo nuevas tecnologías y mejorar mis habilidades.

Por último, pienso que es importante mencionar mi gusto hacia otras culturas y en especial los idiomas, lo que me ha permitido obtener un nivel de inalés fluido.

Experiencia Profesional

Grupo Cincoveinticinco: Ingeniero Front-end

Abril 2020 - Mayo 2022

Desarrollar y mantener software in-house y software dedicado para la producción de series y películas por parte de cadenas de cine y televisión usando varios lenguajes, plataformas, frameworks y herramientas como JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, Material, Ruby on Rails, entre otros.

Asimismo, proponer e implementar arquitecturas y soluciones frontend para los requerimientos solicitados por diferentes clientes como Netflix, Sony Pictures, Telemundo, RCN Colombia, etc.

Freelancer: Desarrollador Front-end

Febrero 2019 - Marzo 2020

Diseño, desarrollo y mantenimiento de interfaces de usuario de aplicativos empresariales usando técnicas y herramientas como HTML5, CSS3, Angular, SASS, Bootstrap, Animaciones SVG, servicios REST, entre otros.

Actualizar aplicativos y páginas web tipo legacy a nuevas versiones usando herramientas web más recientes. Asimismo, trabajar junto a compañias locales como Casa Luker, Igb y Tybasoft.

Universidad Distrital: Desarrollador Software Jr

Enero 2018 - Julio 2018

Administración y mantenimiento del aplicativo web interno usando herramientas como Angular, JavaScript Laravel y MySQL, de acuerdo a las necesidades del software interno y en especial el del proyecto "Conocí-siento".

Adaptación y desarrollo de modulos existentes para generar reportes y productos finales.